(We Are in Our Element)
- Nice to see you, everyone. - It's nice to see you all.
Well, is it possible for a TV show...
to get their ratings as high as 9.6 percent these days?
You're suddenly bringing up the TV ratings?
- We just said our greetings. - Well,
- I didn't mean to... - Let us bring that up for you.
(The dutiful son, Moomoo, decided to move to Gimpo, )
(so he could be near his mother.)
Gosh, it will be too far for you.
(He ambitiously went house hunting without telling his mother...)
(to find the dream house for his filial duty.)
You have to move there now.
- He must move. - That's always the conclusion.
Given the results,
I ought to fulfill my filial duty more frequently.
- Right, you must fulfill your duty. - Hyun Moo.
You're going to set the frequency...
- based on the TV ratings? - Seriously.
My mother loves it. She cares about the TV ratings more.
We'll be able to see you being the dutiful son soon.
His segment got high TV ratings.
It will happen within this year.
If I do it too frequently, it won't look sincere.
I'll do it when the weather cools down.
Okay. My gosh.
But I'm happy to see you here.
Everyone said that...
- you wouldn't be on our show. - Right.
- Me? - Yes.
(As he shared the news of his wedding, )
(Jang Woo said goodbye.)
(It made everyone teary-eyed.)
My mother asked me if she should send some flowers.
- Why? - She thought I was done too.
- My gosh. - I see.
- The tears left an impression. - So...
I told her that I could be on the show before my wedding.
We all thought they wouldn't be on the show after the tears.
But they kept joining us including Dae Ho.
Actually, whoever cried...
- came back to the show sooner. - Gosh, of course.
- Right. - Dae Ho...
(That's why I came back sooner.)
(Jang Woo comes out while carrying a heavy bag.)
My gosh. What's that?
(Looking determined)
(Tossing)
- What are you doing? - What's that?
- What's wrong with you? - Is it someone else's bag?
Did you steal it?
- What's he doing? - Did he steal it from someone?
(Joking)
(Ripping)
This looks like the back alley.
Gosh, what's wrong with him?
(He keeps ripping the bag without saying a word.)
Gosh, this looks good.
It looks like a black market deal.
I see. This part here got all rusty.
What's going on? What?
I think I can still use this looking at the condition.
It had the gear for skin and scuba diving.
Skin and scuba diving?
I've neglected them for a long time,
so the zipper was rusted and they were stuck.
How long had it been since your last one?
About 5 to 6 years?
- It had been a while. - Yes.
The marine products are in danger today.
(Dive into Joy)
(He takes out the gear for scuba diving after 7 years.)
I can still use this.
(He rummages through his gear, stirring memories from the past.)
You're going scuba diving today, but look at your gear.
- Right. - Can't you get them repaired?
I could get them repaired. So I decided to take them with me...
and check.
(He loads everything in the car.)
Let's go. Gosh, it's hot.
(He sets off somewhere.)
(He goes scuba diving after 7 years.)
I started skin and scuba diving a long time ago in 2013.
I was completely crazy about it. That was all I did for five years.
When I was young, I loved the sea.
When I was in my 20s,
I used to sit by the water without doing anything special.
- You really love the sea. - I love the sea.
I have the Open Water Diver certification. What do you have?
I'm certified to teach.
(He has the instructor's certificate.)
- I... - Wait, you have a certification?
I do.
But I can only go as low as 20m.
- Why do you have that? - You?
- It was trendy back then. - Open Water, not First in Line?
- I was the first in line for it. - Open Water...
- I always try out everything. - Yes.
(The TSM tries out everything at least once.)
(He loved swimming ever since he was in his 20s.)
Gosh, look how swift he is.
- You can do the butterfly stroke? - Yes.
- Right. A long time ago... - There's our dugong.
(He learned scuba diving in 2013.)
(Underwater has become his favorite place in no time.)
- Gosh, he loves the water. - I do.
(Happy)
- You can also drive yachts now. - Yes.
(Dugong Jang Woo hasn't changed for a long time.)
- He's a great swimmer. - He is.
I did it every day for five years.
You must go diving over 300 times...
- Gosh, 300 times? - to be certified to teach.
Then you become an instructor.
How many hours would 300 dives take?
Naturally, I decided to go for the instructor's certification too.
I got the instructor's certification.
But at one point, I got so busy with work.
I sort of forgot about the romance of just sitting by the sea.
That's when I stopped scuba diving.
That's higher than the advanced certification, right?
- Okay. - I can teach and give people...
- the Open Water certification. - Right. You're an instructor.
- I see. Really? - You can take me along then.
If you can certify someone, it means...
- That's the highest level. - It is.
(The instructor heads to the sea after 7 years.)
It rained so much up until yesterday.
(The weather looks great.)
It's the last...
- of the holiday season. - Right. It's no joke.
Gosh, there are so many cars.
(But he can't conceal his excitement.)
But it must be fun there.
It's great.
Yes, Gangwon Province is the perfect place.
(Goseong)
- Goseong. - Goseong.
It's the sea.
(The blue ocean stretches out before his eyes.)
Gosh, it's been a long time.
I'm finally here.
What? There are so many people.
It's located by the Ayajin Beach of Goseong in Gangwon Province.
I went to...
- a skin and scuba diving shop. - Ayajin Beach.
(A clean-water spot at the edge of Gangwon Province)
(Ayajin Beach)
(The clear water and clean sandy beach...)
- Goseong and Gangneung... - It's in Goseong.
- are trending these days. - Right.
Hello.
Hello. Did you already go for a dive?
Yes.
- Hello. - Jang Woo!
- Hey! Hello. - Jang Woo, it's hot today.
- Who's that? - You sound like you know her.
- It's so hot today. - Did you already go for a dive?
No, not me. I have customers here.
- Gosh. - Really?
You!
How dare he fire me?
(She was in dramas such as "Pasta" and "My Too Perfect Sons.")
(She established herself as the scene-stealer.)
My gosh. That was a long time ago.
Jae Suk is my senior actress.
She and I got the Open Water Diver certification together.
We practiced in the swimming pool and told ourselves we'd go to Jeju.
So we did go to Jeju Island together...
and went for our first dive.
Afterward, we were together every day for several years.
We did that for years together.
I'd call her up and ask, "Should we?"
Then we went to the sea.
We didn't even book a room or anything.
We slept for a bit in the car and went for a dive.
- You were serious about it. - We floated around on the ocean...
for five hours and had fun.
We were just floating around the water, but we loved that.
(They were just happy to be on the water all day.)
We did that every day.
Everyone said that I was literally crazy about the ocean.
That's how much I loved it.
When I asked if she was going for a dive,
she'd say we should go to the Ayajin Beach.
That was like our rule.
I asked to go somewhere else.
But she always chose the Ayajin Beach.
So we ended up coming here every single time.
- Sir! - Hey.
- My gear... - Yes.
That's her husband. He's totally the man of the ocean.
It's been so long.
I couldn't even zip it open, so I had to cut it.
I had to cut it open. They were all rusted.
I can still use this, right?
- Gosh, it's been a long time. - Yes, it has.
This won't be easy. You know?
Will I be able to fit into any suit?
- The dry suit won't fit, right? - The dry suit?
It doesn't fit me either!
- I can't even put my feet in it. - Right.
Same here. It gets stuck on my feet.
Not even my feet.
I wonder if this will fit.
- Gosh. - Give him a big one.
It's been a while.
Jang Woo, try that one on.
Thank you.
- Let me get changed. - You should get changed too, honey.
(Let me give it a try.)
I wonder if this will fit me.
(Struggling)
(Screaming)
(Panting)
Gosh, it won't fit.
- It won't fit. He will rip it. - It won't fit.
- Did you put it on? - Were you able to wear it?
Did you put it on?
- Gosh. - Oh, my. Hey.
(Looking towering)
- I think he lost some weight. - They're like tights.
(What do you think?)
Can you move around in it? That's good.
What a relief.
This looks good, right?
Jae Suk. Right?
You look cute.
- Why do you look so cute? - Why are you wet?
- I had a hard time putting it on. - Isn't that too long?
I sprayed water.
The fishing village chief heard you were coming...
and dropped off some whelks.
- Really? - So I could eat them with you.
The president of the sea.
The chief also gave us some squids he had caught.
- Just regular squids? - The live ones.
(I love it.)
- He's loving it. - Let's go for a short dive...
and enjoy a long night.
- It's so hot. - Wipe your face with a towel.
Here you go. Wipe your face.
Before we set sail, we need to prepare the life jackets.
- I'll bring them right away. - Okay.
Wet your face too.
- Did you do it? - I did it.
I'll be back.
- Jang Woo, did you eat? - No.
- Don't you get seasick? - I don't get seasick at all.
- Not at all? - No.
That's crazy. I always get seasick.
- What's that? - Something for my seasickness.
I'd get more seasick if I go on an empty stomach.
- That's for your seasickness? - It's for her seasickness?
- It's a simple meal. - That's great.
- Right? - Yes.
I boiled eggs too.
- Gosh. - Let's just eat two.
- I really thought it was medicine. - I see. Me too.
I thought, "That's a lot."
Aren't I thoughtful?
(Aren't I thoughtful?)
I have peaches too. I washed them, so you can eat the peels too.
Can I have one banana? Thank you.
Gosh, you're well-prepared.
(He peels it off right away.)
Right. We need to have something light,
so we can come back, cook, and have a fun time.
(She takes a bite too.)
Isn't it good?
Her nickname was also Dugong.
- Her nickname was Dugong? - Yes.
We were just crazy about the sea.
They said we were like the dugongs.
- We were Dugong Siblings. - Dugong Siblings.
(Dugong Siblings are hooked on bananas now.)
I do see a resemblance between you two.
- Right. - Yes.
In a few days, it will have been 13 years...
since we started coming here.
- That's crazy, right? - My gosh.
- You and I... - Since we began coming here?
Came here for the 1st time on August 18 in 2013.
- She remembers everything. - That was our first day.
I told you I didn't like this place and wanted to leave.
But you wanted to eat jjajangmyeon before we went.
We ended up settling down here after jjajangmyeon.
- Right. The one with fried eggs. - Yes!
I played a big role in their marriage.
(They got married thanks to Jang Woo.)
Did they meet as divers and then get married?
- Yes! - He was running the diving shop.
She and I visited so many beaches after getting our certification.
Then we ended up at his shop.
She didn't like his shop and wanted to go somewhere else.
But I suddenly craved jjajangmyeon.
- So we ordered jjajangmyeon. - Okay.
I was hungry, so I wanted to eat that before we left.
Then he sat down with us and started talking to us.
They got to know each other then and the rest is history.
When people go scuba diving,
they often meet the one they'll marry.
- Right. - Seriously.
- I've seen that a lot. - Of course.
We made this. Have something cool.
- What's that? - It's sikhye.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- He's so sweet. - Her husband is so sweet.
He's taking good care of you two.
- Jang Woo, you can use this. - Yes.
- This? - Yes.
It's the same one as yours.
But it was recently used. So you'll take this.
I'll load the gear on the boat.
- I'll do it. - Wait here.
No, I'll go.
- My husband does everything for me. - Seriously.
How will I live without him?
He's the guy who's always on the move.
(He's the guy who's always on the move.)
Guy Always on the Move.
He's such a sweet guy.
When he's with her, he's even sweeter.
(He kept on taking care of her without even a moment to sit down.)
- He didn't sit down for a second. - Right.
He didn't.
He really never sits down.
He does everything for her.
Wipe your face with a towel.
They speak with honorifics to each other.
When I watch them, I get so jealous.
But he's been like that for 13 years.
When I said I'd do it, he always told me not to do anything...
because I'd only get in his way.
People like him...
- Right. You shouldn't do a thing. - have to do everything themselves.
- Right. - That's helping.
A few years ago,
- didn't we go diving together? - Right.
- We went in after cleaning. - Right.
- He's indeed busy. - "Guy on the Move."
(He checks Jang Woo's rusty gear.)
Let me inspect them.
I'll take care of that.
The equipment weighs over 20kg.
I can't see his face because he moves around so much.
He's too fast too.
- He's super fast. - I only see the back of his head.
(He prepares the gear with incredible power and speed.)
Jun Haeng...
used to serve in an intelligence command.
- What? - What?
I heard that the organization...
had a lot of individuals with incredible talents.
He possesses many skills.
He can climb up Mount Seorak in the blink of an eye.
He's good at every sport.
He does everything himself.
He's an incredible guy.
- That explains his agility. - Yes.
And when he walks,
it's as if he was walking on clouds.
It's like he's flying.
He knows all the geographical features underwater.
- That's impressive. - Yes.
(The origin of his past had been unusual.)
His gaze is different.
There's intense energy in his gaze.
Honey, did you grab a mask?
I prepared everything.
- What's that? - Isn't this amazing or what?
- What's that? - What is it?
- Lee Palm Oil? - Yes, she got my name on it.
- I see. Oh, my. - She had one made for me.
- That's so cool. - Right?
- Gosh. - That's so cute.
- Thank you. - You can wear it while swimming.
It didn't cost much.
(Touched)
She gave me a present.
- Gosh, so cute. - So cute.
- My gosh. What? - What?
- She looks like Catwoman. - Catwoman.
I'm good.
So cute!
(Looking round)
Jang Woo, it looks good on you.
A fat mouse.
(Dugong Siblings are ready to face the ocean.)
- Gosh, that must be fun. - It's really fun.
It must've been a long time...
- since your dive, right? - Yes.
Please get ready, Captain Ha.
Okay.
Everyone, check on your gear.
If you have it, we'll set out.
(Captain Ha sits behind the wheel.)
- Hello. - Hello.
There always must be at least one person on the boat.
- So another captain joined us. - I see.
Could you untie the rope?
I did it.
(Steering)
Push the boat, please. Jang Woo, push it.
- She's good at operating the boat. - She can drive a boat too?
- Gosh. - That's a basic skill.
This looks fun.
My gosh. Skills like that are basic for people like them.
You're stepping on it.
(The boat operated by Jae Suk sets out.)
- Have fun. - Good luck.
(Giggling)
Safety!
It looks like you're joining a Children's Day event.
He reminds me of the show, "Comedy Big League" too.
He sort of looks like a rookie comedian.
(Perfectly in sync)
(The rookie comedian, Dugong, looks innocent.)
The air feels cool.
(Comedian Dugong sets out to the water.)
(Sailing powerfully)
Gosh, the weather is amazing.
Oh, my. Check out the color of the ocean.
Gosh, how strong. Jae Suk.
You're so strong when you drive.
She's so cool.
Captain Ha is a great driver.
(Jae Suk's boat heads to the deeper part of the ocean.)
They must drive far into the ocean.
I thought they'd do it around the seawall.
But there's a lot to see around the seawall in Goseong.
Beginners come and go for a dive around the seawall.
And some divers drive out far.
- I see. - Okay.
It always feels great to set sail on a boat.
It makes me feel like I'm going out for a big challenge...
or an exploration.
The beaches in Goseong are great for skin and scuba diving.
Do you know Ulsan Rock?
You can see similar rocks in this part of the ocean.
- Right. - Yes.
When there are rocks, there are seaplants.
When there are seaplants, fish live around them.
It's fun to look at these things.
There must be rocks...
- There's a lot to see. - for fish to come and settle down.
- Seaplants live there too. - Right.
- Octopuses live there as well. - Okay.
Without them, there can't be an ecosystem.
I didn't know...
you were this knowledgeable about something else other than food.
Right?
You've been on the show for five years. I've never seen you...
- This... - talk so much about besides food.
- What's going on? - This is...
- His answers aren't greasy at all. - Right.
- He didn't hesitate at all. - Right.
You sound so knowledgeable today.
(Today, he's a knowledgeable diving expert.)
(The diving expert is sailing on the ocean.)
I love it. It's been so long.
- What? - I love it.
Me too!
Let's go!
(Dugong Siblings are excited to be close to the water.)
Gosh, look at the people.
That's the Ayajin Beach.
(The Ayajin Beach is packed with summer vacationers.)
- These days... - Goseong is trending now.
(Gathering data)
(As they get closer to the diving spot, )
(he gets nervous and excited at the same time.)
- You must be nervous indeed. - Right.
- It had been a while. - It had been a while.
Is it the red thing over there?
Jang Woo, you see the rope over there, right?
- That's the diving point? - I see. They marked the spot.
Grab it. There's a hole.
- Turn. - Turn.
- There you go. Nice. - There you go. Nice.
Let's grab it.
(I still got it.)
(This is the diving spot of the day.)
- This looks fun. - I see. There's a rock.
When you go to the ocean in other parts of Korea,
you'll see a lot of sand on the bottom.
If there's only sand, you can't see anything...
- when the fish move around. - Right.
But with rocks, the water will be clear.
You know some stuff, Hyun Moo.
Gosh, I used to like diving too when it was trendy.
How many times did you go diving?
Once.
You only went once?
It's like a one-day class then.
(She can't believe him.)
It's...
We'll go down this way.
Jang Woo,
- make sure to clear your mask. - Okay.
Can I put it on in the water?
Yes.
What's that?
There's a lift like an elevator.
(An elevator)
- Really? - There's an elevator.
Put it on there.
It's easier to put it on in the water.
I see. You have to wear more things in the water.
You can't put it on outside the water.
You must wear it in the water.
I didn't know there was a lift.
It's cold only in the beginning. It gets better.
Okay.
- He takes good care of you. - He does.
Is Jang Woo a baby?
It's okay. You're good.
The gate is open.
(They're fully ready at last.)
I'm scared.
I'll go in first.
- Okay. - Go ahead.
- Are you ready? - Take this.
Whatever is comfortable for you...
(He dives in without hesitation.)
- You go in first. - Gosh.
My gosh, this feels cool.
(Dugong Jang Woo is about to go in for a dive after 7 years.)
(Determined)
(He dives in without hesitation.)
(Dugong Jang Woo returns to scuba diving after 7 years.)
I'm getting excited.
- That must be so fun. - Oh, my.
That's called a BCD. It controls buoyancy.
When you add in air, you float up.
You reduce air when you want to dive deeper.
(Jae Suk dives in next.)
This feels so refreshing!
(The siblings are super excited.)
Aren't you cold?
- No. - Not at all.
This is perfect.
We'll go underwater from here.
Make sure to hold onto the line.
(On his signal, )
(everyone goes under the water.)
I'm curious about what's underwater.
- I want to see fish. - Yes, fish.
(Off to the mystical world of underwater)
(Holding tightly)
She helped me navigate.
(They dive deeper while relying on each other.)
(Looking around)
(He reunited with his friends from the East Sea after 7 years.)
- Gosh, that's fascinating. - You can see things so clearly.
- There are so many fish. - You can see so clearly.
When I went into the underwater gorge,
I came across numerous sea urchins.
When I saw those sea urchins, my first scream went off in my head.
(Pop-eyed)
After the sea urchins,
I saw a panther puffer.
- So cute. - That's cute.
- A panther puffer. - That punk, panther puffer.
(After seeing the mystical ecosystem before him, )
(he moves closer, as if spellbound.)
A sea squirt.
A starfish.
- A sea slug. - I see. A sea slug.
(Jang Woo, come and check this out.)
- Gosh, it's an abalone. - An abalone?
(That's awesome.)
Gosh, you can see a lot of things there.
- Yes, it was clear. - Right.
Gosh, this feels surreal.
(The beautifully captivating sight...)
(encourages him to get closer...)
(and closer.)
I'm curious.
(Mystical-looking coral reefs)
It's like watching the documentary,
- "Wonders of the Sea." - Yes.
It's seriously mystical.
That's right. It's like the background image in Windows.
It's so fancy.
It's very quiet when you enter the sea.
Before nature,
I always feel humble.
I entered the sea for the first time in a while.
Do you know the sound of the sea?
I hear the sound of fish breaking things.
I hear the sound of things colliding.
(The sound of things colliding)
My ears pick up such sounds very easily.
I feel like I'm in space. Whenever I saw the sea in the past,
I thought,
"I'm at a place mankind can't explore."
(The feeling of being at a place mankind can't explore)
It's seriously mystical.
(By the way, where is Jun Haeng?)
(Jun Haeng came up to the surface.)
(He takes off his gear and prepares something.)
What? Did he go that far?
- He isn't wearing the gear. - That's...
- Is he freediving? - He's freediving.
Really?
(He turns around abruptly.)
(He dives deep into the sea without any gear.)
(Meanwhile, the Dugong Siblings are having a happy time.)
There are so many fish.
It's nice.
(It's this big, Jae Suk!)
(Diving)
(Jun Haeng suddenly appears.)
- He entered without any gear. - He doesn't disappoint.
(He grabs something.)
Jun Haeng is a licensed harvester.
I see. That makes sense.
- Really? - You need a license to do that.
It's called the freedive harvesting permit.
He's like a diver who harvests seafood.
- He can harvest seafood at the sea. - Right.
- It has to be done without gear. - Without gear.
Other divers are prohibited from harvesting seafood.
- It's prohibited. - They can't touch the marine life.
I see that you need a permit to harvest seafood.
(He comes out of the water and takes a deep breath.)
- It's called collecting. - Collecting.
- That's what he does. - Yes.
My goodness. Look at that.
That must be fun.
It's so nice.
(After harvesting seafood, )
(he comes out to breathe.)
Does he go back and forth?
He goes back and forth.
- He needs to breathe. - That's right.
(He goes up and down for a while.)
There were so many sea urchins.
(We should go up now.)
(Laughing)
He has lost his mind. He's excited by himself.
I love it so much.
I bet it was really fun.
It was so nice.
- Seriously. Hey. - I saw a fish this big.
I saw an abalone this big.
That's how people lie about the size of the fish.
Other people can't go in there.
When you see something in the water, it appears 30 percent bigger.
So I heard.
That's right.
(He takes an elevator to get back on the boat.)
I'm sorry. It must be hard on you.
(Elevator, I'm sorry. It must be hard on you.)
- Thank you. - Okay.
(He takes off the heavy gear.)
(Why did he go back into the water?)
It's cool.
This is fun.
It's so cool.
It looks fun.
(He lets the waves carry his body.)
He looks so free.
I love the floating sensation.
I think I needed good energy...
I got whenever I visited the sea in my 20s.
Wearing my clothes,
I floated in the sea for five hours.
I felt like the sea was consoling a sullen friend.
(As if it was consoling a sullen friend, the sea hugs him.)
I was visiting after a long while,
so I felt a dopamine rush.
It really looks like you're visiting your hometown.
Yes.
How does it feel to visit the East Sea after a long while?
- You're good at diving. - This is romance.
We should eat this much.
- Oh, my. They look tasty. - My goodness.
I saw an abalone that was the size of your face.
Here's the abalone that's the size of my face.
(Screaming)
- It looks tasty. - It looks tasty.
It's nice to visit the sea again.
- That abalone is big. - The abalones were really big.
- Well done. - Well done.
Let's leave after a taste.
(Let's leave after a taste of the freshly-harvested seafood.)
- This connection is precious. - Seriously.
A harvester friend is very precious.
A harvester friend is rare.
It's legal for him to harvest seafood.
- Divers can't harvest seafood. - Divers can't do it.
He can do it because he has a permit.
- He shucked it right away. - Will they eat it right away?
My goodness.
It's big.
They won't even need soy sauce.
(They enjoy the seafood tasting on the boat.)
Jun Haeng, go ahead.
- Jang Woo, try it. - Okay.
- Cut it in half. - Eat it whole.
- It's the best. - No, cut it in half.
Here.
Cheers.
- What? Shall we put them together? - Cheers.
(Cheers for abalone.)
Isn't it tasty? It's tasty.
- It must be firm. - Seaweed is tasty in this region.
It must be tasty.
(Rubbing)
- It's tasty enough to bring tears. - It's tasty, right?
- Of course, it's tasty. - I bet it tastes amazing.
(What's the next menu the harvester is preparing?)
Sea pineapple.
(Plump sea pineapple)
- Gosh. - Gosh.
(Being a harvester, he cleans it in no time.)
It looks tasty.
(It goes straight into her mouth.)
- My goodness. - She ate it right away.
I'm so jealous of Jae Suk.
(Jang Woo takes a bite as well.)
It's tasty, right?
He cleaned the live seafood, right?
We had a live abalone on the spot.
We also had a live sea pineapple.
When I ate live seafood as soon as it was cleaned...
(Let's think.)
I thought, "This deserves three Michelin stars."
You used a new expression.
- I expected to hear "Thick." - I expected him to say, "Thick."
Wasn't the seafood thick?
"Thick" isn't the right word.
- It isn't thick. - It isn't thick.
- It isn't thick. - I'll tell you why it's different.
When seafood enters a fish tank...
- Does it lose its taste? - It begins to starve.
- That's right. - It starves for 3 to 4 days.
- It's hungry seafood... - Hungry seafood.
Versus full seafood.
Seafood also feels exhaustion from traveling.
- Exhaustion from traveling. - Of course.
- It gets tired. - It gets exhausted.
- It gets exhausted. - I bet it gets shaken up a lot.
It gets very exhausted during its journey to Seoul.
- It bumps into things in the car. - Yes.
The fresh seafood gave me so much energy.
Do you want a taste of the sea urchin roe?
(Yes.)
All right.
- What's that? - He cut the sea urchins.
My goodness.
When you eat it like that...
(A dugong meets a sea urchin.)
- Rinse it once. - It's okay.
- Is it okay? - I'm sure of it.
Sea urchin roe.
(Slurping)
It's tasty, right?
- It's nice that he enjoys it. - It isn't fishy, right?
It's like cream sauce.
- Really? - It's thick, right?
It's like fresh cream.
(Sea urchin roe is a rare ingredient...)
(since 1 sea urchin only yields 5 to 10g of roe.)
(It's characterized by a clean taste with the aroma of the sea.)
Sea urchins are harmful to the sea.
- Sea urchins? - Yes.
- Really? - Sea urchins ruin the sea.
- Really? - Don't they help the sea?
- They eat seaweed. - Yes.
They're very tasty because they eat all the good ingredients.
There are so many sea urchins inside the sea right now.
- So they need to be harvested. - They multiply in summer.
- Yes. They need to be harvested. - Let's eat them up.
(Let's eat up the sea urchins for the environment.)
I'll give you a spoonful.
- Shall we go back? - Yes.
(Captain Ha sails the boat on their way back as well.)
(They set off after snacking on seafood.)
(You're good at sailing the boat.)
He always praises his wife.
Seriously.
This is nice.
Gulls!
(Gulls!)
(They pass by a colony of gulls...)
(and enter the port.)
Jae Suk, you've become a fishing villager.
- What? - Seriously.
Once the boat reaches the port, it'll bump into the edge.
Then secure it with a rope.
Okay.
(He stands at the front to secure the rope.)
Go slowly.
Hold onto something. The boat will bump into the edge.
This is scary. Jae Suk.
- Oh, my. - My goodness.
(My goodness)
(It's nothing to a fishing villager.)
Jae Suk, where are you going?
(Calm)
She parked it well.
- That's right. - Did you secure it?
- She parked it very well. - I did it.
You're supposed to do it in a tough way.
Well done.
I don't understand why I'm starving.
Why am I so hungry? I haven't done much.
- They haven't eaten a lot. - Let's rinse the gear.
I don't understand why I'm starving.
Jang Woo, rinse the gear.
- It's time to rinse the gear. - You do it right away.
Yes. Otherwise, it becomes rusty.
Salt makes things rusty.
(They quickly put away the oxygen tanks.)
- I'm starving. - Let's wash up quickly and eat.
Okay.
(He walks over to somewhere.)
(He opens the trunk.)
(He brought things from Seoul.)
He brought many things.
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry too.
Seriously. Why am I so hungry?
- Jang Woo. - Yes?
There isn't anything special. We just have a bigfin reef squid.
- Jun Haeng caught it. - What? A bigfin reef squid?
- He caught it and froze it. - A bigfin reef squid?
It's a bigfin reef squid.
(Big)
It's rare.
I've never heard of it before.
- I've never heard of it before. - Really?
How much is a bigfin reef squid?
- It depends on the season. - That's right. It depends.
- Yes. They can't be farmed. - No, they can't be.
- That one was this big. - I've never seen one so big.
He caught it this morning.
These are whelks.
They're tasty when you boil them in water.
- Whelks. - They're really tasty.
- This one was caught today too. - This one?
- What's that? - An octopus.
My goodness.
Let me see its face.
- Oh, my. It's coming out. - My goodness.
- It's alive. - It's alive.
- It's big. - It's big, right?
Watch out for the ink.
- It's the tasty size. - You have to eat it.
- Shall we boil some water? - Okay.
I... Hey.
Go back inside.
- I'll bring a burner. - We need a cutting board too.
He's light on his feet.
- He'll get sick. - He's working again.
(He helps with everything.)
(The world's number 1 man who is the lightest on his feet)
Towels.
He brought condiments.
- Ice... - Jang Woo, shall we steam it?
- We could steam it as it is. - It'll be so tasty.
- Right? - Let's do that.
- That sounds good. - Gosh, this is...
I had originally planned to make stir-fried chicken and seafood...
as well as seafood and jjajang rice.
But since the weather was so nice,
the captains gave us a squid...
and an octopus.
- There was no place for chicken. - That's right.
(People at the sea village are so generous.)
I plan to cook the squid as it is in the water.
I want to make seafood jjajang.
- Jjajang sounds amazing. - Yes.
- How should we cook the squid? - Let's put it in jjajang.
- Will you add a bigfin reef squid? - It's buttery and tasty.
- A bigfin reef squid? - What do you think?
- Bigfin reef squid jjajang? - What?
A bigfin reef squid is very expensive.
- We can't do that. - But we didn't buy it.
We caught it by fishing.
- A bigfin reef squid in jjajang? - It's unbelievable.
- Is there a cutting board? - Yes, there is.
To be honest, I need to ask someone.
Honey, where is a cutting board?
Where is a cutting board?
- You always go, "Honey." - Honey.
Give it to me.
Jun Haeng doesn't talk much, but he keeps moving.
(The man who's light on his feet was rinsing the octopus quietly.)
Please give me a cutting board and a knife.
I'll bring you a cutting board soon.
(Running over)
He's a giver.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
It's windy. Hold on.
- Is there instant rice? - No.
Honey, is there instant rice?
- There's instant rice. - There's instant rice.
- He's so loving. - I don't know what we have here.
I just know how to drive and dive.
I'm so jealous.
This couple is so cute.
A couple that lives like that...
- by the sea looks nice. - The sea couple is charming, right?
- That's right. They're nice. - The sea couple.
You can go there as the broom-to-be.
- As the broom-to-be? - Yes.
(Bride and groom-to-be)
(Broom-to-be)
- You have a point. Okay. - You can do that.
"Honey, I love you."
"I love you too."
You can do the same thing. "Honey, bring me a cutting board."
Then you can bring it.
After ten years on I Live Alone...
(Broom-to-be can do everything alone.)
You need to turn it on.
- I'll do it. - Give it to me.
(Handing over)
(He hands over the cutting board and begins to set up the burner.)
- Here. - He set everything up.
- Jae Suk cooked a lot. - She cooked.
I bet she's good at cooking.
- Yes, she's good at cooking. - Yes.
(Jang Woo adds the meat he brought from Seoul.)
Gosh, the onions are strong.
It's proper jjajang.
- It's like ganjjajang. - It's nice.
It's like ganjjajang.
- Shall I add the octopus as it is? - Yes.
- Will you boil it as it is? - There you go.
Well done.
It's so thick.
- The knife... - Watch your hands.
- Shall I bring you gloves? - No, it's okay.
He's so sweet.
- Is the knife sharp? - My goodness.
The knife is sharp, but this squid is so thick.
Shall I bring you a bigger knife?
I'll do it.
What? I'll do it.
Did he make a big mistake in the past?
What are you talking about?
- How is that possible? - He's just good to his wife.
- How is that possible? - Seriously.
I've known them for 13 years, right?
- He has always been like that. - You know,
the recipient of such care needs a matching personality.
(After seeing Joy's brother-in-law who was the sweetest man, )
(he passionately talked about his firm belief in marriage.)
You need to meet someone like that.
Someone like me would go, "Leave me be!"
"Don't do anything!"
If the recipient does that, his attentiveness will be wasted.
- They need to be a good match. - It takes teamwork.
- They need to be a good match. - Yes. They need to be a good match.
It's so slippery.
Honey, do you want to do it?
Yes.
(Yes, of course.)
How do you want me to cut it?
Just make it fit into the pot.
- They lead fun lives. - It looks like...
they already have roles to play.
- I love how they use a polite tone. - I think...
Jae Suk can do things by herself.
But she just likes to do them with her husband.
(The man with light feet slices the squid skillfully.)
You're good.
(Oh, my!)
Does the octopus need to be boiled for a long time?
I asked the captain.
He told me not to blanch the octopus like they do in Seoul.
If you boil it for too long, it'll be tough.
- No, but... - No.
Right? KEY, how should you boil it?
You should boil it for 5 or 40 minutes.
- That's right. - It should be over 30 minutes.
- You know the Spanish pulpo dish. - Pulpo.
It's tender because they boil the octopus for an hour at least.
They use boiling water.
But in Korea, people prefer...
- blanching the octopus. - They blanch it.
- They parboil it. - Koreans prefer a firm texture.
- You need to boil it for long. - The pulpo dish is tender.
Yes.
- It's very slippery, right? - Yes.
Is it too thick?
It's good enough.
It's just right, honey.
(What a sweet comment!)
They speak so sweetly to each other.
Wipe your sweat.
Thank you.
I'm so jealous.
(Jang Woo is absorbed in cooking.)
(The whelks join the octopus.)
They're huge.
They look appetizing.
It's like chicken and seafood soup.
- You're right. - Exactly.
- I'll go and wash it. - Okay.
(Shall I start cooking the bigfin reef squid jjajang?)
This is so much fun.
Is that oyster sauce?
Oyster sauce.
Oyster sauce is a must for Chinese food.
(He adds sugar, another indispensable ingredient.)
Do you make jjajang like that? That's incredible.
My goodness.
- He's adding chili powder. - It's the Sichuan style.
It's the Sichuan style.
Cheongyang peppers.
(He even adds Cheongyang peppers to cut down the greasy flavor.)
Look at him.
So that's how you make jjajang.
Jjajang is tastier when it's spicy.
That's right.
(The base for Sichuan jjajang is complete.)
How old were you when you began to cook so well?
I didn't know much about cooking...
- when I was with you. - That's right.
- I just know how to eat. - You didn't believe me...
when I told you that I could cook well.
You were like, "That's nonsense."
- Gosh. - Gosh.
- You're good. - Gosh.
Gosh.
It looks tasty.
(He adds a smoky flavor for Jae Suk and Jun Haeng.)
It looks so tasty.
- Here you go. - Jang Woo, he brought a chair.
Jun Haeng brings everything.
He's so quick-witted.
- What is it? - Bigfin reef squid is going in.
- Is it okay to add so much? - Of course.
- We'll eat it anyway. - That's right.
I added bigfin reef squid pieces like that.
- It's expensive. - It's really expensive.
- It's unbelievable. - Does it taste different?
It tastes completely different.
When you eat a bigfin reef squid, it tastes like...
- it contains butter. - That's right.
You feel like you're chewing butter.
The buttery flavors come out when you chew the squid.
How fascinating. Why is it so different?
(The detailed description makes him feel dizzy.)
(Jang Woo coats the bigfin reef squid in red.)
It looks so tasty.
It smells amazing.
(The incredible appearance makes them sit down.)
We're watching from the first row.
- It looks so tasty. - It makes me modest.
Seriously.
I'm finally getting a good look at his face.
- It's my first time seeing it. - Really?
(They finally see his face.)
Oh, my.
Gosh, you're no joke.
- He's really good. - Right?
It's really hard to do that with a wok. That's heavy.
(Impressed)
(He pours chunjang over the half-cooked squid.)
- It's the smell of Seoul, honey. - Gosh.
- This is so... - I can't believe it.
He looks happy.
(Get excited for a surprising taste!)
I think I've seen this somewhere in China.
Gosh, right. I look like a Chinese cook.
(Dugong's bigfin reef squid Sichuan jjajang)
I'll bring the plates.
Stop bringing them now.
(I'll taste it.)
- Gosh, look at the squid. - Gosh.
Look at how thick it is.
Is it good?
Is it incredible?
(Frowning)
(There's no need to talk about it. Hurry up and give it a try.)
It's amazing. What do we do?
It's so good.
This makes me feel worse as I can't buy that.
Exactly.
- The bigfin reef squid is... - It's amazing.
Really? I should give it a try.
It's hot.
(He gets excited about the first bite...)
(as he has been moving around a lot.)
It's incredible, isn't it?
- Gosh. - That looks really good.
It's a bit better as I don't know what it tastes like.
(Rationalizing)
The bigfin reef squid...
gave the jjajang an unbelievable massivity.
He finally used a different word from "thickness."
(His vocabulary improved from "thickness" to "massivity.")
There was a strong taste of the jjajang...
and the spiciness of the Sichuan sauce,
but the essence of the bigfin reef squid...
brought everything together.
The essence of seafood.
Done.
This is done.
- Gosh. - There was the octopus too.
My gosh.
That broth can't be put to waste.
Gosh, look at how tender it is.
Be careful as it's hot.
It might get on you. Hold on.
Gosh, it's huge.
(Steaming giant octopus)
We should get all of the whelks too.
It doesn't need to be seasoned as it was freshly cooked.
Would you like to try some?
(Heart pounding)
(Laughing)
(Freshly cooked)
The octopus.
Gosh, it looks so tender.
It does look really tender. Gosh!
It will be really good.
(Experiencing a new world)
There's Jang Woo's signature expression.
It really made me go wild.
In Seoul,
the octopus is blanched slightly.
But I was told that the octopus shouldn't be blanched slightly here.
I heard that people who lived by the sea boiled it for quite a while.
To be honest,
I've tried a lot of octopuses of all kinds of sizes.
The octopus I had today...
was on a different level.
It felt like it was soaked in a flavor enhancer.
It's perfectly seasoned, right?
(You should also have a bite of the octopus too.)
Say something.
(Satisfied)
It's cut like this.
(Plopping down on his seat instead of saying something)
It doesn't even feel tough.
(I should try a bite as everyone is enjoying it.)
(Taking a big bite)
(Dugong takes another bite as well.)
It's like bubble gum.
Why is it already seasoned?
It was seasoned by nature.
It was eaten before getting put into the tank.
There's no need for any chojang at all.
There's no need for chojang.
It can be eaten as is. It will already taste seasoned.
(Feeling proud)
- What is that? - What is that?
- The squid. - Gosh, the squid.
Gosh.
- Should we cook all of these? - Yes.
Let's cook all of them.
(Become tastier.)
How many packets of ramyeon should we make?
- Just 3. - Just 3? Okay.
There's ramyeon too?
(Three packets of ramyeon that can't be missed)
Are you serious?
Oh, we have sea urchin roe too.
- Oh, we have sea urchin roe too. - Sea urchins!
I'll get the sea urchin roe.
Here I go!
He's the man with the lightest bottom in the world.
Here I go.
- What is that? - What is that?
- Gosh, that's a lot. - Sea urchin roe?
How many were caught?
(Hurrying)
Here comes the best dish.
- Gosh, did you prepare all of this? - Yes.
You prepared it so neatly.
(Amazed)
Did he prepare the sea urchin roe all day long?
I'll open the lid of the pan with the squid.
(The squid was steamed nicely in the meantime.)
The squid looks plump.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- Gosh! - That's the tastiest size.
- I love that size. - Same here.
Shall we make the ramyeon right away?
We'll get everything out first.
We can just pour the water in there.
And use the same broth?
- Right. - There you go.
- That will be nice. - It's a seafood broth.
(The ramyeon and soup powder get added in without hesitation.)
We should put in the prettiest one.
(The prettiest squid gets added in.)
(Boiling)
This is exciting.
(The steamed squid gets cut into nice pieces.)
- You're lucky with food. - You really are.
The seafood was brought in that day.
- Exactly. - Right.
(The steaming ramyeon is ready as well.)
- Put it right there. - Here?
Gosh, thank you so much.
- Gosh. - Gosh, it looks delicious.
(It holds the taste of the sea that was enjoyed the whole day.)
- It's a feast. - My gosh.
That's worth diving in.
(Chewy steamed squid and whelk)
- Look at its thickness. - That's what you call thickness.
(Thick steamed squid)
(Dugong's bigfin reef squid Sichuan jjajang)
That's insane.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
(Refreshing and spicy squid ramyeon)
- There are so many dishes. - Gosh.
Gosh, how much is all of that worth?
The sea urchin roe.
(Finally getting a taste of the seafood feast)
When else would I try this?
Eat it in one go.
(A spoonful of sea urchin roe)
Gosh, that must be good.
(Finding him to be cute)
He's hilarious.
His nostrils became bigger.
- That must be amazing. - It had such a great scent.
It tasted really tender and fresh.
It was like freshly squeezed milk.
I don't drink milk these days.
Have you tried freshly squeezed milk?
- Are you a calf? - Freshly squeezed milk tastes sour.
- Are you a calf? - You wouldn't be able to have...
- It tastes sour. - freshly squeezed milk...
as it wasn't sterilized.
I got a bit too ambitious and got ahead of myself.
(I got a bit too ambitious.)
- I almost cried. - Really?
- So this is happiness. - I feel like crying too...
as you're enjoying it so much.
- This is great. - Eat it with the warm rice.
Eat as much as you want.
Should we try Jang Woo's jjajang?
Sure. Let's try Jang Woo's dish.
We should have this.
Eat a lot of this.
- Eat a lot. We'll eat jjajang. - The dish from Seoul.
We'll have a lot of the dish from Seoul.
(Jang Woo enjoys the food from the East Sea thanks to them.)
- We prefer those dishes. - Right.
He's feeling touched after every bite.
(Jun Haeng gets a good amount of the jjajang.)
(He places it on his wife's plate first.)
(The man with the light bottom has light chopsticks as well.)
(Eating the jjajang served with love neatly)
- Gosh, the jjajang is amazing. - Really?
Gosh!
My gosh.
(It tastes even richer with his perfect seasoning.)
The jjajang draws in the rice.
(Feeling proud)
Take a bite of the squid ramyeon too.
(Desperate)
Gosh!
It's the squid ramyeon.
(Dreams come true.)
Gosh! Stop it.
So you can pick that much food with chopsticks.
As the ramyeon was boiled in the squid broth,
- It tastes totally different. - the noodles didn't get soggy.
- You're right. - The noodles are chewy.
(Jae Suk takes a bite of the chewy squid ramyeon too.)
- Gosh. - This is how it should be cooked.
- This is how it should be cooked. - Gosh.
- Gosh, I'm so jealous. - They really look like siblings.
(The Dugong Siblings eat just like each other too.)
I will experience a bit of extravagance.
- Go ahead. - Eat all you want.
There's another bowl if you need more.
The sea urchin roe was placed on top of the ramyeon.
- Gosh. - That's unbelievable.
Placing it on top of the ramyeon?
(Slurping)
(He tastes the extravagance with his eyes closed.)
(Amazed)
Cheese ramyeon.
It became just like cheese ramyeon right away.
(Clean and savory sea urchin roe just like cheese)
I don't think you will gain any weight with food like this.
You're wrong. You do gain weight.
You'll be in big trouble if you think that way.
I gained so much weight after coming here.
(Taking a bite of the steamed squid after being ready to gain weight)
My gosh.
(Satisfied)
It's so savory.
Right.
This tastes like crab innards.
(The squid innards taste like crab innards.)
That can be eaten only when it's fresh.
(Freshness spread inside his whole mouth)
You should have it.
(Sweating)
There's so much broth coming out from him.
It was really tender.
It was full of flavor...
and it had the saltiness of salt.
(Letting out a breath for the squid)
(Just like the younger Dugong that is happy, )
(the older Dugong targets the squid.)
So it's eaten without any chojang.
There was no need for any.
We have squid all the time,
but I keep wanting to have the jjajang.
- The jjajang is good, isn't it? - Would you like some more?
You should have it. I'm okay.
My gosh.
We finished it already.
(Finishing a bowl of jjajang in a flash)
Gosh, it was finished already.
(Satisfied)
You should eat a lot. You have work tomorrow.
It'll be tough.
(Astonished)
Hold on.
(He gets up.)
By the seawall.
- What's that? - What is it?
What? Why did you get something so expensive?
- Is it from Seoul? - I can't tell who these are for.
- "Is it from Seoul?" - "Is it from Seoul?"
The big one should be for me.
No.
- Here you are. - Thank you.
Gosh, he's so caring.
(Feeling proud)
They're matching.
- It's perfect. - Right.
I saw it, and it reminded me of him right away.
Right. It looks great.
It's perfect for him.
- That's a smart gift. - It's cute.
- Thank you. - Gosh, you don't need to thank me.
We should use them when we go to the valley.
(Feeling proud)
Gosh, we should eat more.
(We should eat more as we feel great.)
I finished the jjajang.
(Eating the octopus too)
It's so good.
It's been a while since I've seen you...
and you're still the same.
The same goes for you.
You two are eating and seeing great things together,
- so you haven't aged. - What are you saying?
We're soon going to turn 50.
We're almost 50.
- Were you that old? - Yes. I was born in 1979.
I'm from the Class of 2001.
- What? - She's the same as me.
- She looks really young. - Right.
I'm from the Class of 2009.
Were you born in 1986?
I told you.
Why did I think that you were around my age?
I thought that too.
It's because we hang out in similar ways.
- We enjoy similar things. - Right.
I really thought he wasn't that much younger than me.
- I had no idea. - I'm still 40 now.
(I'm still 40 now.)
Gosh, I saw him when he was in his 20s.
It's time for you to ripen now.
- I've ripened a lot. - Right.
(I've ripened a lot.)
He has ripened.
Lost in the fantasy alone.
We made spicy seafood stew with all of the people around.
I went around a lot with Jang Woo.
- We went to Tae Island too. - Right.
- We went to a lot of islands. - Right.
I'm quite certain about this.
The sea to me is my 20s.
- It's your youth. - My memories of my 20s.
My car, camping gear, and everything I had...
was focused on the sea.
That was how close I lived to the sea.
That's impressive.
I was really crazy about the sea.
As I age year after year,
I live the same way I live...
when I work or meet people.
But as I received this great energy today,
something that was stuck inside my head got relieved.
I was able to revisit my memories of my 20s...
and learn how to be humble before the sea.
It was great.
The abalone is this big!
The sea didn't change at all. I should visit more often.
Right!
(The Sea Here Again)
(I Live Alone)
(The Link Between You and Me)
(Is Ju Seung heading somewhere?)
Gosh, you're wearing a dress shirt.
It had been a while since I had an appointment.
Gosh, so this is it.
It's big.
(Peeking)
- Where are you going? - Where is this place?
It's the Brachiosaurus.
- "Brachiosaurus?" - All of a sudden?
What's this one?
(Natural history museum?)
- Seodaemun? - There's a place like this...
in Seodaemun?
This would be really scary to meet.
(A vicious creature protects the natural history museum.)
(Looking intently)
I would faint if I actually saw this.
I was always very interested in dinosaurs.
The new series of "Jurassic Park" was released,
so I went to watch it. I ended up falling for them even more.
I recently got invited to a film festival in Dallas...
and that was why I went to the US.
There was a natural history museum there...
and it was really big.
- It does look really big behind. - It's massive.
They actually dig out fossils there.
- Really? - Yes.
You can see people digging fossils out behind glass walls.
The place that appeared in "I Am Museum?"
"Night at the Museum."
- Oh, right. - "I Am Museum?"
What's "I Am Museum?"
That's "I Am a Natural Person..."
and "Night at the Museum" mixed together.
I like movies that start with "I am."
- "I Am Museum." - It sounds like a documentary.
I was totally mesmerized.
I wondered if there was one in Korea and found this place.
There was a place like this in Korea?
So I have to line up here.
This place is really popular even during the weekdays.
- Hello. - Hello.
- One ticket, please. - Right.
It's Culture Day today, so you get a 20 percent discount.
- Oh, right. - Yes.
You look much better in person.
Thank you.
She offers lip service to him too.
(Joking)
(Beeping)
(He pleasantly enters the museum with the compliment.)
Amazing.
Gosh, it's big.
(It's grand.)
(Eyes opening wide)
(An overwhelming sight)
(The dinosaurs Ju Seung wished to see are all gathered.)
It's set up really well.
That's the headbutting dinosaur.
- The Pachycephalosaurus. - Right.
I heard that its skull was 20cm thick.
(He greets the massive dinosaur bones.)
That's the Acrocanthosaurus.
It means it's a lizard with tall neural spine sails.
- You know a lot. - It's a theropod.
There are saurischians...
- Saurischians? - and ornithischians.
Under the saurischians,
there are theropods and sauropods.
Do you know what "dinosaur" means?
(Do you know what "dinosaur" means?)
- "Dinosaur?" - "Dinosaur?"
- "Dinosaur?" - I don't have a clue.
- "Dinosaur?" - Doesn't "saur" mean "lizard?"
- Right. - Right.
Is it "scary lizard?"
- You're right. - What?
- What? - Really?
(He got this right?)
- Congratulations. - Nice one.
(Moomoo gets it right.)
"Dino" means "scary."
- Right. - "Saur" means "lizard."
- I see. - "Scary lizard."
Did you know that birds are dinosaurs?
Pterosaurs.
- All birds? - All birds.
- Right. - Even sparrows...
- and pigeons. - Even chicks?
- They're all dinosaurs? - Yes.
Are they descendants of Pterosaurs?
No. Pterosaurs aren't dinosaurs.
- Pterosaurs aren't dinosaurs? - They're different.
Really?
It's massive in scale.
It's fascinating.
We were constantly exposed to them starting from a young age...
and it didn't feel that fascinating.
There are actually a lot of fascinating creatures around us.
Giraffes have long necks.
Lions and tigers are fascinating too.
But dinosaurs were even more fascinating.
There was a creature that was 80t.
The bite force of the Tyrannosauros...
is strong enough to bring down an elephant.
- Gosh. - How would it be...
if they were still alive?
This is the Argentinosauros.
It's the tallest and biggest dinosaur.
The Tyrannosaurus is this big.
That's a big difference.
The Argentinosauros is 11 times heavier.
It must've been like a lion fighting against a giraffe.
No matter how strong the Tyrannosaurus is,
it will be put down with one hit of the neck.
It's fascinating how there were massive creatures in scale.
That is why I'm greatly interested in dinosaurs.
Do you know how they stood up with such long necks?
- I wonder. - How did they stand?
- With its neck? - Their bones were empty.
- They're fake bones? - I see.
What do you mean by that?
So their bones were light?
- Like birds? - Right.
That is why birds are considered to be dinosaurs.
Let's go up.
(He moves upstairs to see his favorite dinosaurs.)
Life Evolution Hall.
Everything is set up really well.
Gosh, there are a lot of people.
There are a lot of children.
There must be a lot of children as they are on vacation.
You know how children are as smart as professors, right?
- They know all of the names. - They know everything.
I memorized all of the names in elementary school,
- but I forgot all of them now. - Right.
(I'm here to see dinosaurs on my own too.)
What is that?
(Looking intently)
It's the story of the Mesozoic Era.
The creatures of the Triassic Period were very small.
Knowing about dinosaurs means a lot.
They have a massive and rich history.
They were separated as the Triassic Period,
the Jurassic Period, and the Cretaceous Period.
Around when the Cretaceous Period ended,
- an asteroid hit the planet. - Right.
There was an explosion that occurred 66 million years ago.
That was when the Cenozoic Era began...
and led up to the generation of us humans.
There are a lot of theories based on that.
- There are different theories. - That's one theory.
There are those who say that isn't right.
That's the most believed theory of the extinction of dinosaurs.
- But it wasn't fully proven. - It wasn't fully proven.
- There's the ice age theory too. - Right.
- There are a lot of theories. - There's one based on...
- a volcanic eruption too. - Right.
Earth is known to be around 4.5 billion years.
If 4.5 billion years is thought to be 24 hours,
us humans have only lived for four seconds.
- Right. It's really short. - But as for dinosaurs,
they have lived for up to one hour.
They are our great seniors.
We've only lived for 4 seconds out of 24 hours.
"Why am I alive right now?" I have a lot of these thoughts.
Isn't it fascinating that you're alive right now?
"Why am I alive at this moment during the 4.5 billion years?"
"It's just a split second."
Dinosaurs make me have those thoughts.
This is another thing that was mentioned.
Rain falls and the trees hold up that water.
That water becomes valleys and seas.
It then becomes water vapor and the cycle continues.
The water that we are drinking...
is actually the water that dinosaurs had.
We're drinking the water that dinosaurs drank.
It made me think that we are all connected.
I believe we can know who we are...
if we study about dinosaurs.
Is that even right?
It's true though.
Did we leave him on his own for too long?
(Joking)
I'm certain that we're drinking the same water.
(Firm)
The history of living creatures.
(Looking for the link with dinosaurs who are our great seniors)
(Looking intently)
Dragonflies are our seniors too.
They were around since 300 million years ago.
Dragonflies were this big back then.
Right.
I heard they were big because of the high oxygen concentration.
Right. I heard that.
All other insects were big too.
I heard that. It's fascinating.
(He continues to look around in search of fascinating facts.)
Troodon.
(There are so many fun things.)
Wait. It's a child docent.
I should ask the expert.
What? A child is a docent?
Children are experts there.
(Children are experts in dinosaurs.)
Not many fossils were found,
so there isn't enough evidence.
Let's move on to the next one.
- We'll check out the Tyrannosaurus. - He looks smart.
(Following the docent)
Tyrannosaurus means...
a violent lizard.
Compared to its body size, it has small arms.
Its arms are only 1m long,
but they can exert as much as 200kg of power.
He's so cool.
They're not randomly selected.
They're interviewed too.
- It's systematic and professional. - I bet it's really competitive...
because there are so many knowledgeable kids...
- in that field. - Yes, there are so many.
Let's move on to the next one where I'll explain...
about the Elasmosaurus, which you can see over there.
The Elasmosaurus's total length extends to as long as 10m.
It's about 2t heavy.
Its neck is 7m long.
Its neck is 7m long?
The main feed of the Elasmosaurus...
is ammonites, which you can see over there.
It can eat huge ammonites.
So they eat ammonites.
They also ate fish.
- He memorized all that. - That's right.
What's even more amazing is that he's holding himself back.
That's right.
Because the listeners wouldn't understand.
- Then is Elasmosaurus... - Yes?
The descendant of sea turtles?
Its neck can support its body in the ocean,
but outside the water,
- it can't due to gravity. - He knows everything.
If you look at its neck, it totally looks like a snake.
That's right.
Then can't it crawl on the ground like a snake?
- I'm not sure about that yet. - Like this.
It can't?
What do you think?
(Me?)
He's flustered.
I don't think its neck is that strong.
- So it can't come out of the water? - No.
- It stays in the ocean only? - Snakes use their body,
not their neck.
He's an expert.
(He has a clear, confident voice on dinosaurs.)
You know a thing or two about animals.
I'm a docent too, but I didn't apply for today.
He's a docent for the Paleozoic era.
Oh, the Paleozoic era.
- What's next? - I'll explain about Triceratops.
Gosh, Triceratops.
Triceratops...
I used to love Triceratops.
Triceratops are cool.
It's as long as 8 to 9m.
And it's as heavy as 5 to 9t.
At one point, Triceratops...
had the best optimized mouth and teeth...
for a carnivorous diet.
Some paleontologists claimed that,
but not many fossils to support that claim were found,
so we're not certain about that.
What I found cute was Triceratops.
Actually, I like Triceratops.
It's sweet and charming.
We're the Dooly generation, after all.
We believe dinosaurs are sweet.
But actually, they'd tear us apart...
if we met them.
So we prefer sweet ones.
(We prefer sweet herbivores.)
Let's move on to the next one, and I'll explain to you...
- Oh, it's Stegosaurus. - Yes.
- I used to like it too. - It looks sweet.
Stegosaurus...
is as long as 6.5 to 7.5m.
And it's as heavy as 5.3t.
- It's pretty heavy. - Yes.
Since its head is this small,
isn't it less smart?
It is believed so,
but Stegosauruses were surprisingly smart.
It has a small brain,
but the prejudice against small brains was eliminated.
They thought it was less smart...
because it had a small brain,
- but it turned out to be smart. - That's right.
Just because the brain is small, it doesn't mean you're dumb.
(He understood it.)
He even knew about the past and the current information.
Like, how it used to be and how it has changed.
The knowledge we used to have on dinosaurs has changed a lot.
The knowledge we had from "Jurassic Park..."
is completely different...
from the one we have from "Jurassic World Rebirth."
When they assembled its bones,
they thought it dragged its tail.
But think about it.
If you drag your tail around, it'd hurt.
But now, its tail is tilted and held up.
- It's lifted from the ground. - He's right.
They used to draw dinosaurs like this.
How did they find out that it lifted its tail?
The tail fossils weren't found.
There must be a trace of it dragging its tail around,
- That's right. - but when its fossils were found,
- there were only footprints. - There were only footprints.
So it was proven that it lifted its tail around.
It'd have lifted its tail?
Because there were only footprints?
The appearances of dinosaurs we know of...
could all be changed.
They could be completely different from what we imagine.
We'd never know. You know how human skulls don't have noses.
- You're right. - You're right.
We only guess its appearance from its bones.
- That's right. - Right, we can only guess.
I think it's an uncharted field.
(The more you learn, the more mystic its world is.)
It has a small brain, and its skull is hard.
That's how it can protect its brain.
There were four times as much carbon dioxide.
It ate a lot, so its body must've gotten big.
- Yes. - Right?
You're right. It swings its tail like a scorpion.
(Bingo!)
Anyway, animals have their own characteristics.
They were passed down.
They are related to humans.
There are many animals that are instinctively related.
As for our members,
Hyun Moo is close to Pterosaurs.
Pterosaurs have armor-like bodies.
Their bodies are swollen.
- They're puffy. - Look at that.
- They're quite similar. - They're similar.
- What is that? - I mean...
Its tail is its weapon.
- That's right! - It swings its tail to attack.
- You're right. - It uses its tail...
like an iron mace.
- You're right. - It's a strong one.
I wouldn't say it's strong.
- It hits after holding back a lot. - That's right.
At once, like this.
- It suits him. - Yes, it does.
Na Rae is like a Triceratops.
She's cute, and she has lats.
They're really wide.
- Her lats are really... - I think they got bigger.
As for Jang Woo and Sung Hwan with big builds...
They're like Argentinosaurus.
- It's as heavy as 80t. - He's right.
As for Kian84... There's a really nimble one.
Is it Allosaurus? There's one that always runs.
(They have similar instincts to run.)
They're similar.
KEY is close to a Stegosaurus.
There are the ones that look like a chicken.
They're a little agile.
(He's somewhat agile.)
Sung Woo is close to a Pterosaurs.
- Among them, - That's right.
- he's like a Pteranodon. - They're similar.
- They're similar. Good one. - It suits him.
Then which dinosaur...
do you like the most?
- Gosh, it's a difficult question. - Me?
I like...
Well, I like Elasmosaurus.
- The one with a long neck? - Yes.
Yes.
What's the reason?
Because it has a long neck,
I found it quite cool.
I thought it was cool,
but after looking at its face...
It's become less likable now.
- I like it less now, but... - It's less likable now?
- Yes. - You keep changing your favorites.
Which dinosaur do you like the most?
I like Pachycephalosaurus.
Why?
It's the cutest because it's small.
- Because it's cute? - Yes.
- Is your school on break? - Yes.
- Which grade are you in? - I'm in the sixth grade.
Really?
They're quite small.
I find small ones cute.
You're doing something amazing when you're young.
- Thank you. - It was amazing. Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
I'll go for the Paleozoic era next time.
- Keep up the good work. - Goodbye.
Seriously...
There are so many living things.
(Heading somewhere after enjoying the exhibition)
What's this?
- A merch shop. - Right. A merch shop is a must.
You must get one.
(You can't walk past this place.)
- You must go. - You must buy one.
That one is cute.
There are so many things here.
Gosh, it'd win over kids' hearts.
(Ju Seung carefully takes a look at each item.)
You can't walk past this place.
That's right.
Wait. This is cute.
(I'll get this too.)
They were of such good quality that I kept wanting more.
Merch from museums these days are quite good.
Does it glow in the dark?
(Does it glow in the dark?)
- I loved luminous items as a kid. - That's right.
- I love luminous items. - Right.
Why did we love them so much?
This must glow in the dark.
I should get it.
Gosh, they're quite detailed.
They're well-made.
- They're quite nice. - Gosh, they're really long.
(Grabbing another one)
My mom used to scold me when I grabbed things like that.
- Of course. - That's right.
- You can only get 1 among them. - Right. You can get only 1.
(Heading to the counter after grabbing a bunch)
Gosh, seriously...
I'll get this poster too.
This is the fun of being a grown-up.
You feel proud of yourself in such moments as a grown-up.
It's 108 dollars in total.
You got a lot of things.
I couldn't get a dinosaur toy even if I wanted to as a kid.
Thank you.
(Looking around)
(He heads back to the exhibit hall instead of going home?)
Wait.
(Where is he going?)
Sir.
- Oh, it's a gift? - Yes.
- I got you a gift. - Sorry?
Pick the dinosaur you like.
(A gift of gratitude for the docent)
(Gosh, it's my favorite dinosaur.)
- It's a gift. - Thank you.
(Feeling proud)
It's a volunteer work for him,
so I really wanted to give him a gift.
That's such a cool volunteer job.
I only did recycling for a year.
Let's go.
(Setting off after filling himself with the energy from dinosaurs)
(Glancing over)
Gosh, that's a Pterosaur.
It does look like a Pterosaur.
- This is really... - You're right.
Ju Seung can be romantic.
(Moved)
What? He's not going home?
(Romantic Ju Seung heads to somewhere else.)
Lottery?
Hello.
You still want a big win.
Do you buy lottery tickets often?
No, not often,
but on days when you feel small...
Why? Because the docent was too superior in knowledge?
No, it's not that.
After seeing the Paleozoic, Mesozoic, and Cenozoic era,
you realize we've only lived for four seconds, figuratively.
- That's right. - So you feel empty.
- We're only like dust. - I thought I needed...
dopamine in such moments.
I go there when I want to cope with emptiness.
Through lottery?
(Dumbfounded)
You wouldn't even look at a dinosaur if you win.
(Taking something out)
(He takes something out from the phone case.)
I'll exchange this for a ticket.
- To this? - Yes.
- Oh, my. What is that? - What's that?
You won?
- Really? - The tickets I won.
(Repurchasing lottery tickets with the 9 dollars he won)
(He secures a seat and sits down.)
Please...
Let's see.
If there's a number...
that matches the lucky number...
(The lucky number is 7.)
(He wins if he gets another 7.)
There is one!
- What is? - What is it?
I won from the first round?
Seven.
Oh, number seven? You win if there is one.
- He won one dollar. - Gosh.
- I won 1 dollar. - You get 2 dollars if there are 2?
- No, you must scratch to find out. - Oh, my. It's one dollar.
Oh, it's written down.
The price is written.
- Oh, the price is written? - That's right.
Gosh, how amazing.
(He keeps the momentum going to the next ticket.)
(I need to get number 5.)
You lost. Goodness.
(He loses in a row, failing to fill the emptiness.)
(This time, he pays more effort into it.)
- Gosh, it's eight. - He won.
- What? How much is it? - Yes, he won two.
Darn it.
(He won a dollar again.)
(A dollar)
(It's a shame that it's only a dollar.)
- It was only a dollar. - It does give you a dopamine rush.
I think he'll win about five dollars.
I bet he'll win ten.
Gosh.
I'd win 500,000 dollars if I get either 2 or 6.
- Gosh. - It says 500,000 dollars.
Do you win 500,000 dollars if you get 6?
- I win 500,000 dollars if I get 6. - That's right.
Oh, that's the lucky number.
Six.
Five or six.
That's very intuitive.
It gives you the biggest dopamine rush.
Right. You can find out right away.
(Desperate)
Saurus.
(Please let me win.)
Please... What?
What is it?
Is it round?
(Is it number 5, the number he desperately wanted?)
(This is nerve-racking.)
(Here we go!)
What?
- Isn't that five? - Five?
- I win 20,000 dollars if it's 5. - Gosh, 20,000 dollars.
What?
(Please...)
- Isn't that five? - Five?
- I win 20,000 dollars if it's 5. - Gosh, 20,000 dollars.
(It's 3, not 5.)
- Still, you won five dollars. - Five dollars.
- It's five dollars. - Seriously.
- That's not bad. - Nice.
If it's five dollars...
You broke even.
I won 7 dollars after spending 9.
- That's not bad. - I won seven dollars.
You used two dollars for the dopamine rush.
It's not bad.
Gosh, this isn't easy.
(I wanted to fill dopamine as I felt empty.)
Can I exchange it for the Lotto ticket?
You can't find out the result right away...
if you get the Lotto ticket.
- I see. - You spent all the money.
I feel like the store owner is holding his laugh.
Have a good day. I'll come again.
I could win Lotto.
So what happened to your Lotto ticket?
- I didn't win any. - Goodness.
He wouldn't be here had he won.
(That's not true.)
(The time he hovered between his dream and the secular world)
(Ju Seung returned home.)
Gosh, I haven't seen Ju Seung's house for a while.
He still has the same lights.
- The house where I pooped. - Exactly.
Gosh, I'm so hungry.
(He became hungry after doing a study on dinosaurs.)
What is he going to eat?
Is he going to eat something related to dinosaurs?
(Thinking)
Something like Yonggari chicken.
- That'd be amazing. - Right?
That'd complete his day.
- That way, it's consistent. - Yes. Yonggari chicken sounds nice.
(Did he take out Yonggari chicken from the freezer?)
- Oh, it needs to be thawed. - Buckwheat soup?
You use the single-handle pot well.
- It's really convenient. - There's nothing like it.
That's the best.
(When the water starts to boil...)
(Biting)
- Is it naengmyeon? - It's buckwheat noodles.
That looks delicious.
(After stirring it carefully so it wouldn't stick, )
(he washes it in cold water.)
Buckwheat noodles are the best on hot days like now.
The buckwheat noodles I made...
isn't an ordinary buckwheat noodle dish.
I see.
That's set.
(He opens the fridge again.)
(What is that?)
- What? Watermelon? - What is that?
I think watermelon would suit it.
What? You're adding it?
- What is he doing? - That's a new combination.
I can't imagine the taste at all.
But there are restaurants that add watermelon to soybean noodles.
Yes, there are.
But to add watermelon to buckwheat noodles?
It's cold watermelon buckwheat noodles.
- I see. - Cold watermelon buckwheat noodles?
Someone gave me watermelon,
but for someone who lives alone, it's too much.
You need to finish it in three days once you cut it.
- That's right. - That's right.
- It becomes mushy. - Yes, it's hard to get rid of.
That's right.
Otherwise, you have to keep it in the freezer, but if you do,
it becomes watery.
- You have to blend it, then. - That's right.
I starred in a movie in Japan,
and a dish called Morioka reimen is introduced in the movie.
(Watermelon is added in Morioka reimen.)
It looks great.
They add watermelon as a topping.
His dish feels more reassuring after seeing this.
I was wondering what he was doing.
I was reminded of that dish,
so I added watermelon to the buckwheat noodles.
I think it'll be nice.
- It's nice. - It must be refreshing.
It looks refreshing.
(Adding shaved ice to make it cool)
(Adding lemon juice)
I should add bonito flakes too.
- Gosh, that's proper. - Oh, like that?
(Sprinkling bonito flakes as well)
You should add grated radish too.
(Grated radish)
You have that too?
And wasabi.
Gosh, it looks pretty nice.
(Placing a dinosaur figure as well)
(Cold watermelon buckwheat noodles with a dinosaur)
- Why did you put the figure there? - I know.
The dinosaur figure...
- Is it a dinosaur set meal? - A dinosaur set meal?
You get a toy like that if you order a kids menu.
- That's right. - That's right.
- Like the one from fast food? - Yes.
The Happy Meal.
It's the Happy Meal.
- Happy Buckwheat Noodles. - Happy Buckwheat Noodles.
(Having Happy Buckwheat Noodles with the dinosaur)
In summer,
you ought to have fruits.
Will it be sweet because of the watermelon?
Sweet and salty?
(Taking a bite of the watermelon and buckwheat noodles)
It must be delicious.
(Approving)
(Taking a spoonful of soup)
(Slurping)
(Amazed)
(Flashily twisting the noodles with his wrist)
(Slurping)
It was so good.
I added sourness to the buckwheat noodles...
and had it with watermelon.
It was sweet and sour.
It was refreshing.
It was delicious. Watermelon suits the noodles.
Watermelon doesn't suck in the soup, surprisingly.
It's quite firm.
So it suits the noodles well...
as a topping.
- It doesn't mix with the soup? - It doesn't.
I love naengmyeon with pear.
- Naengmyeon with pear? - Naengmyeon with pear?
It suits the noodles well.
But people don't eat it these days.
- Right. - There's naengmyeon with pear...
and watermelon kimchi these days.
People make use of fruits in various ways.
Adding lemon juice was the kick.
It made the dish really good.
It's refreshing, so it's easy to eat.
It looks delicious.
He cooks well for himself.
(Lifting)
(Slurping)
(Gulping)
(He drinks the soup without even breathing.)
- Goodness. The ASMR... - Goodness.
- The soup must be delicious. - That's nice.
(Salivating)
I'm done.
(He finished the bowl refreshingly.)
He finished it.
(He cleans up the bowl right after eating.)
(Opening)
For dessert...
Let's have this.
(He took out a container from the fridge.)
All right.
- Prune? - Oh, it's prune.
(Eating)
(Impressed)
Californian prunes are delicious.
I must have this for my bones.
(Taking another piece for his health)
- I heard prunes were really good. - Really?
Prunes are really good for your gut.
Prunes are?
They're good for your bones and your bowel movement.
It's good in many ways.
Gosh, in summer,
you ought to eat fruits.
(He's done with the fruit meal course.)
(Touching)
(What is he looking at?)
Oh, they grow when you add it to water.
That's right.
- What happened to them? - They became this big,
but not any bigger than that.
I got magnets too.
(Here they are.)
This is a sticker.
(Hold on, babies. I'll make friends for you guys.)
Here. This is from the Paleozoic era.
The Mesozoic era.
The Cenozoic era.
Yes. That way, you remember them.
Because you forget.
I think history is fun.
You really are quite romantic.
- Yes, he is romantic. - Thank you.
(Grateful)
It has all the dinosaurs I like.
- That's cute. - Stegosaurus.
Stegosaurus.
(Sticking)
Pachycephalosaurus.
Its forehead is 23cm thick.
I'm a human, and I'm living now.
So, it's a combination...
of the Cenozoic era and the Mesozoic era.
It's the Ceno-Mesozoic era.
My house is like Jurassic Park.
My house is like the museum of natural history.
I have everything.
It looks like a home with kids.
Oh, the poster.
It suddenly became a home for kids.
Right. With a poster, it felt like that.
Right? It looks like a home with kids.
- Try sticking a Hangeul poster too. - Right.
Or an English alphabet poster.
- You could also... - For you to study.
Stick the giraffe height chart that measures your height.
- The giraffe height chart? - And the Hangeul poster.
Grown-ups can like the things that kids like.
- That's right. - Yes, you're right,
but it really looks like a home with kids with that.
The poster alone...
- changes the mood drastically. - It had such an effect.
Your home feels warmer.
(Hitting)
- What's that? - What is that?
Oh, I got a dinosaur dig kit from the museum.
You're excavating a fossil at home?
I tried one, and it was fun.
Kids would go crazy for this.
- Of course. - It looks like so much fun.
- It's all in there? - The bones are in there.
Gosh, it's in high quality.
(What kind of history will I uncover today?)
It does look fun.
It must be fun to dig.
I got the hand.
- I got the hand. - Kids must love this.
- They would. - They'd love this.
They'd go crazy for it.
You can really find the bones.
It's of really high quality.
- It looks real. - I know.
People with worries...
play with blocks these days.
It helps you focus.
I think it'd be nice to play with when you have worries.
That's right.
Next time, I want to go to Haenam or Goseong.
There, you can see...
Right, there are actual traces of dinosaurs in Haenam.
That's right! It has the historical site.
(Super serious)
Ju Seung is certainly romantic.
- He has a childlike innocence. - Yes, a childlike innocence.
When he's immersed in something,
- he sees it to the end. - He does.
There you go.
I assembled everything, from the head.
It's Elasmosaurus.
It's a dinosaur with a long neck that looks like a sea turtle.
I think it's a very mystic and charming dinosaur.
Dinosaur toys say they're for six-year-olds or up.
But they don't say six-year-olds or down.
Even if I play with them as a 30-something-year-old,
no one stops me. It's unrestricted.
These days, I have a strong desire...
to find my childlike innocence again.
See? There are things like that.
Just because it's for kids,
doesn't mean grown-ups can't play with it.
- Of course not. - Of course not.
I think it'd be fun...
to find your childlike innocence again from time to time.
Just like Kian84 said, it's really innocent...
how you can immerse in something.
I know.
We all have that deep in our hearts.
I'm still crazy about the "Harry Potter" series.
When I go to their merch shops,
I'd run past kids and get a wand.
- Really? - You can't use it in real life.
It just makes you happy.
- That's right. - You're right.
- It's purely for my happiness. - It makes you really happy.
It's for my happiness.
I think it's like that.
- Yes, like a kidult. - That's right.
- You become a kidult. - A kidult?
(It's fine as long as you keep it in your heart.)
(I'll Live as a Happy Kidult)
(Next story)
(6 award winner from the 78th Tony Awards)
(The writer of the musical, "Maybe Happy Ending")
("Writer Hue Park Wins a Tony Award...")
("for the First time as a Korean")
("The First Tony Award, a Splendid Achievement")
(The first Korean and Asian...)
(to win a Tony Award)
(He's been living alone for 18 years.)
(I'm Writer Hue Park.)
(New York)
(This is Broadway, the sacred place for plays and musicals.)
(Where "Maybe Happy Ending" is held)
(A crowd packed in front of the venue)
(Past the main entrance, )
(he goes to work through the backdoor to the back of the stage.)
(He greets his colleagues in a friendly way.)
(Are you the writer for the show?)
(Yes, I am.)
(Oh, my gosh)
(This is my second time already.)
(As he has enjoyable conversations with the audience...)
(The theater gets filled.)
(The musical starts.)
(I watch the musical nervously every time.)
(My sincerity got through to them.)
(Every audience member gets up.)
(They give a standing ovation wholeheartedly.)
(A feeling that's hard to express)
(Leaving behind the magnificent theater, )
(he heads...)
(to the subway.)
(I feel rushed after the play.)
(Rushing)
(Quicker than anyone, )
(he boils water for ramyeon.)
(Hue's seaweed ramyeon)
(Filled with seaweed)
(You can't resist late-night ramyeon after work.)
(Happy)
(Puffy)
(Shall I do the laundry I've been putting off?)
(A self-service laundromat?)
(I don't have a washing machine at home.)
(It's okay. I can carry it back and forth.)
(Thinking)
(I wish I could carry a house home too.)
(The dream of owning a house)
(When will I be able to own one?)
(Maybe Happy Ending for Me Too)
(I got an extra nine hours today.)
(I'm grateful for today.)
(It's Kian84's miracle day.)
They say a day is long if you get up early.
It's a great thing.
(He welcomes the miracle morning...)
(with great energy.)
(A surge of dopamine)
(With Sean, the godfather of running)
(he starts running along the Han River refreshingly.)
(Panting)
(He runs out of energy soon.)
(How can I run 30km again tomorrow?)
(You have to be here by 4:30am, )
(so get up at 4am...)
(Filling his energy to the full with Han River ramyeon)
(Jumping in refreshingly)
(A desperate struggle for the most productive life)
(To survive, )
(you have to go crazy.)
(A dazed day where you sleep until the evening)
(A miracle morning with blood-shot eyes)
Gosh, I'm tired.
(To Sleep or Not, That is the Question)